A Guide to the Henry G. Kunkel papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA273
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Visual Materials, 1946-1983; 7
  - Prints, 7.1
    - Manuscript: "A Community -Acquired Outbreak of Pneumocystis Carinii Pneumonia, Initial Manifestation of Cellular Immune Dysfunction"? Henry Masur, Mary Ann Michelis, et al., undated (Box 86, Folder 13)
    - Manuscript: "Dem. of ANAE Activity etc." - Knowles et al. - Cell Immunol., 1977-1978 (Box 86, Folder 14)
    - Manuscript: Drawings, Prints, Galleys, Drafts of Figures for Mss. and Slides ? "Genetic Variants of yG4 globulin", 1970 (Box 86, Folder 15)
    - Manuscript: "Expression of Ia-like etc." -Winch et al. - PNAS, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 16)
    - Manuscript: "Glomerular Localization of DNA and Antibodies to Nuclear Constituents", undated (Box 86, Folder 17)
    - Manuscript: "H Chain Subgroups" - Related Charts and Graphs, 1959-1964 (Box 86, Folder 18)
    - Manuscript: "The Human Ia System", undated (Box 86, Folder 19)
    - Manuscript: "Hum. Lymp. bearing Ia etc". - Hoffmann et al. - J. of Imm., 1977 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Manuscript: Miscellaneous Charts & Graphs, undated (Box 86, Folder 21)
    - Manuscript: Misc. Drawings, Charts & Photographs from Various Mss., 1980-1982, undated (Box 86, Folder 22)
    - Manuscript: Misc. Manuscript -Related Charts, Notes & Figures, undated (Box 86, Folder 23)
    - Manuscript: "Mouse Spleen Lymphoblasts Generated In Vitro, Their Replication and Differentiation In Vitro" - Ralph Steinman et al., undated (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Manuscript: "Oxytocic Activity of Purified Vasopressin" -Draft & Notes, 1952 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Manuscript: "Parallel Syn., oflmm. etc." - Mestechy, Winch, Hoff, Kunkel? JEM, 1976 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Manuscript: RA-Urea-Hans, 1956-1958 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript: "A Study of CSF Idiotypes in Multiple Sclerosis" - G.C. Ebers, 1981 April (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript: "Three T-Cell Hybridomas Do Not Contain Detectable Heavy Chain Variable Gene Transcripts" - Mitchell Kronenberg, Ellen Kraig, et al., undated (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Misc., 1975-1983, undated (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Misc. Antigen/Immunology Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Misc., c. 1977, 1981 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Misc. Immunology Notes, undated (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Kunkel Reprints, 1951, 1966, 1975-1985 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Misc. Loose & Untitled Notes, 1982-1983 (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous Manuscript -Related Photographs, undated (Box 87, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1969-1971 (Box 87, Folder 14)
    - Monoclonal antibodies, undated (Box 87, Folder 15)
    - TheÿMurineÿSyngenicÿMixed LvmphocvteÿResponse.ÿI.The Target Antigens Are Self Ia Molecules - Laurie H. Glimcher, et al., undated (Box 87, Folder 16)
    - Notes, Drawer 2 III, 1966, undated (Box 87, Folder 17)
    - Notes: 2 peaks, 1964-1965 (Box 87, Folder 18)
    - Outside Letters, etc. - Unrelated to Current Work, 1973-1974 (Box 87, Folder 19)
    - Photos - "Bence Jones Work" - Drawer 7, undated (Box 87, Folder 20)
    - Photos. Drawer 7, 1969-1970 (Box 87, Folder 21)
    - Photos. Drawer 9, undated (Box 87, Folder 22)
    - Photos. Drawer 9 - X -rays and B2A Myelomas, undated (Box 87, Folder 23)
    - Photos (Laboratory). Drawer 7 (Box 87, Folder 24)
    - Photos (Laboratory). Drawer 7, undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Photos (Laboratory). Drawer 7, undated (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Photos (Laboratory) I. Drawer 5, 1959, undated (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Photos (Laboratory) II. Drawer 5, undated (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Photos (Laboratory) IV. Drawer 5, 1968, undated (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Sa -SLE, 1961-1983 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      Restrcted from scholarly access.
    - Schrohenloher, Ralph E., 1963-1971 (Box 88, Folder 7)
    - Schwartz Paper - PNAS, 1982-1983 (Box 88, Folder 8)
    - SLE (Systemic Lupus Erythematosus), 1961-1977 (Box 88, Folder 9)
    - Slides for Connor Paper, 1952-1953, 1983, undated (Box 88, Folder 10)
    - Special Items, 1957, 1965-1966 (Box 88, Folder 11)
    - Sweden Exps., 1950, 1951, 1957, undated (Box 88, Folder 12)
    - Tan-Connors, 1980-1981 (Box 88, Folder 13)
    - Untitled Laboratory Photos, 1964, undated (Box 88, Folder 14)
    - V. du Vigneaud, 1965 (Box 88, Folder 15)
    - Workbook #13 - H. Kunkel, 1965 September-1966 January (Box 88, Folder 16)
    - Workbook #14 - H. Kunkel, 1966 January-April (Box 88, Folder 17)
    - Workbook #15 - H. Kunkel, 1966 April-September (Box 88, Folder 18)
    - Workbook #17 - H. Kunkel, 1967 January-August (Box 88, Folder 19)
    - Workbook #18 - H. Kunkel, 1967 August 10-1968 January 22 (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - Workbook # 19 - H. Kunkel, 1968 January-May (Box 88, Folder 21)
    - Workbook# 20 - H. Kunkel, 1968 May 28-October 21 (Box 88, Folder 22)
    - Workbook #21 - Dr. H. Kunkel, 1968 October-1969 February (Box 88, Folder 23)
    - Fd Se Mobil (approx. 200 photos) (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Negatives, 7.2
    - Dr. Kunkel, #83-3849, 1983 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - Fd Se Mobil, Untitled Negatives, undated (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - Gels, 1964-1969 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - Idiotype Meeting, 1981 July 13-17 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - Manuscript: Dem. of ANAE Activity etc. - Knowles et al. - Cell. lmmunol., 1977-1978 (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - Manuscript: Misc. Drawings, Charts & Photographs from Various Mss., 1980, 1982, undated (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - Manuscript: Misc. Manuscript -Related Charts, Notes & Figures, undated (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Misc. ca., 1977, 1981 (Box 90, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Manuscript -Related Photographs (Box 90, Folder 9)
    - Monoclonal Antibodies, undated (Box 90, Folder 10)
    - Slides for Connor Paper, 1952-1953, 1983, undated (Box 90, Folder 11)
  - Slides, 7.3
    - Special Items, 1957, 1965, 1966 (Box 90, Folder 12)
    - Book # 1 - Dr. Kunkel, 1979 March 26-1979 December 31 (Box 90, Folder 13)
    - 14 Dr. Koffler - Ouchterlony Plates, 1961, 1971-1972; Fragile. Glass. (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - Fenneke Joslin -B, 1972 June-October; Fragile. Glass. (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - Fenneke Joslin -D., 1973 January-March; Fragile. Glass. (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Fenneke Joslin -D., 1973 January-March; Fragile. Glass. (Box 90, Folder 17)
    - Manuscript: Demonstration of ANAE Activity etc. - Knowles et al. - Cell Immunology, 1977-1978 (Box 90, Folder 18)
    - Manuscript: Misc. Drawings, Charts & Photographs from Various Manuscripts, 1980-1982 (Box 90, Folder 19)
    - Microscope Slides (Drawer 5), Fragile. Glass. (Box 90, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Glass and Plastic Slides, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 90, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Glass and Plastic Slides, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Slide (from desk drawer): Hyland Ra -Test, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Pepsin (p. 30), Fragile. Glass. (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - Photos. Drawer 9, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - Photos (Laboratory). Drawer 7, undated (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Rheumatology, 1968-1982 (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Special Items, 1957, 1965-1966 (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - Sternal Marrow, 1956 August 31; Fragile. Glass. (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - Loose Glass Slides, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 5: R. Carr, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 60-884A: Dr. Rockey, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 61-130: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 62-265A: Dr. Rockey, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 62-265B: Dr. Rockey, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 62-1076F: Dr. Mannik Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 63-0342: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 63-0905: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 63-0977D: Dr. Mannik, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 64-0252A: Dr. Grey, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 64-1188: Dr. Tan, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 64-1229: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 64-2127: Dr. Grey, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 65-412: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 65-1432: Dr. Tan, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 66-1859: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 66-1859: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 67-978: Dr. Koffler, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 67-980: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 67-1364: Dr. Schur, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 67-4522: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 67-4522: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 1072-6: Dr. Deicher, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 1073-6: Dr. Deicher, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 3541-7C: H. Kunkel, 1952 June 24; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 4087-7A: H. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 5934-7: Bearn, 1955 October 19; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 6534-7B: H. Kunkel, 1956 June 7; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 8513-7: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 8513-7: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 9154-7A: Dr. H. Kunkel A: R.Carr, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - D.B.: B._: DNA, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - Dr. Holman/Dr. Deicher: #8813-7C, 1958 December 2; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - Dr. Kunkel: The Rockefeller University, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - Dr. Mannik, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - E5 Acid buffer: C48: DNA and Ph3, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - H. Kunkel: 523-6A, 1955 December 9; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - H. Kunkel: 523-6B, 1955 December 9; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - H.G. Kunkel: 549-6A, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - H.G. Kunkel: 1617-7A, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - H. G. Kunkel: 1617-7B, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - H.G. Kunkel: 3939-7B, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - H. Kunkel: 1803-7b, 1950 June 12; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - H. Kunkel: 3686-7, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - H.G. Kunkel: 7323-7, 1957 June 5; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - H.G. Kunkel: 7610-7A, 1957 October 29; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - H.R. Deicher: 8030-7, 1958 March 21; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - Hypothetical mechanisms in R. arthritis, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - Immunizing Antigens, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - H.R. Deicher: 8118-7, 1958 April 11; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - Kunkel: 1816-7, 1950 June 19; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - 1946 May 17, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - Rising: Nelson, 1946 October 30; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - R.J. Slater: 3004-7B, 1907 November 27; Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - U.B.-V6: D.M.-B.C., Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - U.S. Naval Medical School- Bethesda, MD, Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - Untitled (5 slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 91)
    - #1, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - #3, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - #8 - Brown, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - #14, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - #18, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 62-565A: Dr. Bearn, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 62-565B: Dr. Bearn, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 62-565C: Dr. Bearn, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 62-565D: Dr. Bearn, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 67-757: Dr. Koffler (5 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 67-978: Dr. Koffler (6 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 67-978: Dr. Koffler-8, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 67-978: Dr. Koffler-9, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 67-1447: Dr. Koffler (3 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 67-1447:Dr. Koffler-7A, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 67-1447: Dr. Koffler-7B, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 67-1447: Dr. Koffler-13, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 67-2278: Dr. Koffler (7 Slides) Bic Globulin in SLE, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Case #466-246: yG awb: DNA/DNA block: Dr. A. Bearn, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Dr. Bearn (2 slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Dr. Schur- C. Perkins, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Dr. Schur- J. Brown, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Dr. Schur- J. Brown, SLE, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Dr. Schur- M. Mannik (2 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Dr. Schur- M. Spiegal, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Dr. Schur- P. Adams (2 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Dr. Schur- R. Petty, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Dr. Schur-R. Petty (Rheum. Art.), Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Duration ofincubation (HRS)/ % CPM in PCPT, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Effect of Absorbtion with Nucleoprotein on yG Concentration of DN'ase-Acid Buffer Eluates, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Eluted Antiepithelial Antibody, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - yG in SLE, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - yG- SLE- Dr. A. Bearn, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Injections of I*BSA, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Localization of yG and C'3 in SLE, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Localization of yG in SLE, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Micrograms DNA Added/Micrograms Protein in PCPT, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Rabbits Showing Nephritis/Arteritis After Injection of I BSA, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Renal Disease Associated with Anti-basement Membrane Antibodies, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Renal Disease Associated with Antigen Antibody Complexes, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Untitled Graphs, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - Untitled, Fragile. Glass. (Box 92)
    - 60-485: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 61-1526: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 62-0898: Dr. Rockey, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 62-2302: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 63-0977A: Dr. Mannik, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 64-0929: Dr. Grey (2 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 64-1229: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 64-2127: Dr. Grey, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 65-368: Dr. Solomon (4 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 65-383: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 65-460: Dr. Solomon, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 65-1126: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 65-1166: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 65-1260: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 65-1678, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 65-2166: Dr. Schur (7 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 65-2260: Dr. Schur, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 65-2338: Dr. Prendergast, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 65-3226: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 65-3852: Dr. Kiiiander (2 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 66-830: Dr. Mannik, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 66-1145: Dr. Litwin (2 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 67-434: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 67-1254: Dr. Schur, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 67-1587: Dr. Natvig, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 67-1940: Dr. Natvig, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 67-1945: Dr. Yount (3 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 67-4522: Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 67-1945: Dr. Yount, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - Dr. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - Dr. Kunkel: #1, #2, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - Dr. Kunkel: #3, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - Dr. Kunkel: 65-866 (2 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - Dr. Prendergast: 65-1292, Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - Dr. Solomon: 65-1283 (3 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - H.J.M. Eberhard: 6211-7, 1956 February 24; Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - H. Kunkel: 7668-7, 1957 November 19; Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - Kunkel: 7892-7, 1958 February 11; Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - Untitled (2 Slides), Fragile. Glass. (Box 93)
    - 0.1 Ml Don. Euglob. and 0.2 mL McCurdy Serum: #1559-1, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 621- XX Harrigan RA 2: Serum, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 621- XX Harrigan RA 2: Serum, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 621- XX Harrigan RA 2: Serum, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 731: RA and Serbu. T: 2, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 731: RA and Serbu. T: 2, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 731: RA and Serbu. T: 2, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 731: RA and Serbu. T: 2, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 731: RA and Serbu. T: 2, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 731: RA and Serbu. T: 2, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 731: RA and Serbu. T: 2, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 731: RA and Serbu. T: 2, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 843: Pethl RA Serum: 195-2.71 mg/mL and 213- 1.37 mg/mL, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 843: Pethl RA Serum: 195-2.71 mg/mL and 213- 1.37 mg/mL, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 856: Sicbut: 1-Whoc., 2-Ab., Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 856: Sicbut: 1-Whoc., 2-Ab.-attached document, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 929- B. Soses Serum, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 942: Top-Petty Euglobulin, Bottom- Seibert Euglobulin, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 945: Es. Robertson RA, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 945: Es. Robertson RA, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1027: Padula, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1184-5 and Control 1185: EPI RA 195, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1184-5 and Control 1185: EPI RA 195, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1184-5 and Control 1185: EPI RA 195, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1211: E. Lamotore RA, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1213: Serna thall RA #2, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1229: Petty, 1-2, 1958 January 17; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1306: y Glob.: 19s in Hupo y Glob., Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1306: y Glob.: 19s in Hupo y Glob., Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1306: y Glob.: 19s in Hupo y Glob., Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1306: y Glob.: 19s in Hupo y Glob., Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1519-1: McCurdy: 114 N.S.:, 1958 October 10; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1521-1: McCurdy: 1:1 NS:, 1958 October 10; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1528: Joel Hammond: 1:1 NS: H. Kunkel, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1531-1: Jacq. Hammond: 1:1 and NS:, 1958 October 31; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1557 1: Donnellan Euglob.-Before and After Absorption, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1557 2: Donnellan Euglob.-Before and After Absorption, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1558: Donnellan Euglob. and Pup. Serum, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1563: A- McCurdy Euglob in 5% NaCl and in Acid; B- McCurdy Euglob in NaCl and in Acid, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1563: A- McCurdy Eug1ob in 5% NaCl and in Acid; B- McCurdy Euglob in NaCl and in Acid, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1567: x5 c Phosph. Buffer & 1568: Supernate x15 c H2O, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1567: x5 c Phosph. Buffer & 1568: Supernate x15 c H2O, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1572 (1 & 2): Donnellan (Euglob 2) in 5% NaCl and in 6 M urea complete dissoc., Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1581-1: Mary Garnsey Serum: 1:1 NS, 1958 December 5; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1589: Isol. Don Prot.- Euglob II and Dens. Grad., Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1589: Isol. Don Prot.- Euglob II and Dens. Grad., Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1589: Isol. Don Prot.- Euglob II and Dens. Grad., Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1590-1 (2 plates): Don Ppt (as in 1589): 1:1 NS, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1590-1 (2 plates): Don Ppt (as in 1589): 1:1 NS, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1590-1 (2 plates): Don Ppt (as in 1589): 1:1 NS, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1590-2: Donnellan Ppt (as in 1589, 1590-1): 1:1 7s Leo y glob., undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1590-2: Donnellan Ppt (as in 1589, 1590-1): 1:1 7s Leo y glob.: - attached document, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1593: Don Ppt (as in 1589, 90...): 1:1 E 12M Urea, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1594-2: Pungello Ppt./NS-H20 dilution, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1679: I. Calo Serum, Dr. Pagano; II. Obrien Serum, Dr. Fud, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1684: I. Hammond Euglob.; II. O'Neill Euglob., Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1685: I. Don. Serum .15 and .3 One-Fifth v Polio; II. Don. Serum and Sal., Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1686-1: I. y2 Calo; II. y2 Don, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1686-2: I.v Calo; II. v Don, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1688: I. Donnellan Euglob.; II. Hernandez (RA) Euglob., Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1689: I. Calo Serum and Polio v; II. Calo Serum alone and 1690 (First Frame), Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1689-2: Don v2 (3M in urea); II. Don vz (10.5% in NaCl), Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1692: I. Sosis Serum and Macra .18cc; II. Sosis alone, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 1814, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 2132: Serum Osborne- Macro, Dr. Edelman, Bhl, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 2132: Serum Osborne- Macro, Dr. Edelman, Bhl, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 2392/2399, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 2544: O'Dell Euglob in Acid (I) and Saline (II), Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 2545: O'Dell Euglob in Acid (I) and Saline (II), Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 2970: Osmond VA isol.- Fr. II, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 2970: Osmond VA isol.- Fr. II, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - Donnellan Serum 4/10 - E1554, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - E718: Christian: Whole Serum- 1:1 Thall, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - E1167: Elsia Lamathinh: Def if PT has 22 MAT, 1957 November 12; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - E1180-1: Southall Rheumatoid: Robbins/Frankel (1.3 mg%) 212 ok, 1957 November 26; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - E1180-1: Southall Rheumatoid: Robbins/Frankel (1.3 mg%) 212 ok (related attachment), 1957 November 26; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - E1522: McCurdy: Undiluted D 56ø30", 1958 October 10; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - E1545-1: McCurdy Serum 10/10, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - E1565: Don Prot. Isol. By Don Grad from Euglob- Ba23: Phomogeneous:, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - E1566: DeSousa Serum: 1:1 NS- H. Kunkel:, undated; Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - y Glob: Upper Josephine Mancuso, Fragile. Glass. (Box 94)
    - 612: yG Cutter: 17821, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 612: yG Cutter: 17821, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 613: Stand. vglob. EF y of Ed. Fr., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 613: Stand. vglob. EF y of Ed. Fr., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 613: Stand. vglob. EF y of Ed. Fr., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 673: Whole Serum. XVI Kusch. RA Frudgut LE, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 883: Siebert Zero, 19-208; 22-23ø, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 883: Siebert Zero, 19-208; 22-23ø, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 883: Siebert Zero, 19-208; 22-23ø, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 883: Siebert Zero, 19-208; 22-23ø, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 883: Siebert Zero, 19-208; 22-23ø, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 936 & 937: y Glob.- 1. Soses, 2. Agamma, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 956 & 957: y Soses: 5% NaCl, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1037: 1. Austin Rourke ser. fr. Boston active, 2. Tube 8 ofPosnick cold agglut., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1206: RA ppt. usual E.P. precip., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1206: RA ppt. usual E.P. precip., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1206: RA ppt. usual E.P. precip., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1206: RA ppt. usual E.P. precip., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1206: RA ppt. usual E.P. precip., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1206: RA ppt. usual E.P. precip., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1207: Carter, RR & LE, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1223,1224,1226: 1. Pellegrino; 2.B Bode, B Bode I :4; M.G. IX MSH- Dr. Weismann, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1290: Amylord, Rosenbuy, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1345: American Angelo-LE-2; Arthritis 1462: Serum H. Blatchford (Fries dis.), Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1580-1: DeSousa Euglob., dissolved in 5% NaCI, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1584-1 & 1584-2: Don. Reassoc.-13a25- 1. In urea, 2. Dial vs. N.S., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1584-1 & 1584-2: Don. Reassoc.-13a25- 1. In urea, 2. Dial vs. N.S., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1594-1: H20 dilution: Friedgutppt-N.S., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1600: McCurdy Euglob, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1604: (1-4) Rh.F. and Macro; (5-6) Rh.F. and serum, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1606: (I-3) R.F. and stock serum; (4-6) Control for 1605 (I-3), Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1611: (1-3) Stock norm ser. and macro; (4-6) Stock norm. ser., Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1616: RFc and Stock serum, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)
    - 1618: RFc and v glob. Hicone, Fragile. Glass. (Box 95)